[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
&gt;&gt; Ladies and gentlemen, please
&gt;&gt; 女士们 先生们
welcome to the 2018 Apple Design
欢迎来到 2018 Apple Design Award 设计大奖
Awards.
的颁奖典礼
Please, welcome your host,
有请主持人
Senior Director of Evangelism,
技术推广高级总监
John Geleynse.
John Geleynse
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
&gt;&gt; Well, hello.
&gt;&gt; 大家好
It is great to be back here with
很高兴再次
the Design Awards on the main
回到这个舞台
stage.
揭晓设计大奖
And this evening we've got a
我们将给你带来一个精彩的夜晚
So, thank you for coming out and
所以 谢谢大家前来
joining us in this afternoon and
参加今天下午的颁奖
celebration of the winners that
并对获奖者表示祝贺
we're going to announce, soon.
一会我们就会揭晓答案
We're here to honor developers
我们在此表彰
who have done excellent work and
在技术应用和创新方面
with technology adoption, with
做得十分出色的开发者们
innovation, making their apps
他们让自己的 App 变得十分独特
And in my role at Apple and in
多年以来
my team's role at Apple we've
我和我的团队
worked with so many of you over
一直在与你们共同努力
the years, helping you to create
帮助你们创造出
great apps.
更好的 App
Apps that are engaging and apps
更夺目 更吸引人的 App
Apps that are high performance
表现更佳的 App
and apps that are, honestly,
甚至是无可挑剔的 App
And so, it's an honor for me to
所以 我非常荣幸
be here and to be able to lead
能在今晚主持这场典礼
this award ceremony and honor
并嘉奖这些优秀的开发者
The work that is done by you, as
作为开发团队
the developer committee, speaks
你们所做的工作
to the heart of Apple.
体现着 Apple 的核心
And that heart is, as we all
这个核心
know, creativity.
就是创造力
In all of its forms, we believe
不论以何种形式 我们都相信
that creativity has always been
创造力永远是
humanity's greatest super power.
人类最伟大的超能力
And when it combines with
当它与技术结合的时候
technology great things come to
会创造出很多
life.
很棒的东西
Incredible things come to life.
和不可思议的成果
And that's why we feel deeply
这就是我们为什么由衷地认为
that you, as developers, are
作为开发者的你们
amazingly creative.
拥有惊人的创造力
Like a paintbrush to an artist,
相较画笔之于画家
chords to a composer, words to
和弦之于作曲家
an author, code is an even more
文字之于作家 代码是一个更加
advanced creative tool.
具有创造力的工具
Because it can really do and
因为它的确能够
create so much.
完成和创造许多事情
As developers, you're developing
作为开发者
on the canvas of the entire
你们以整个世界为舞台
world causing great new
开发了许多
groundbreaking apps and ideas to
开创性的 App
take shape.
提出了很多绝妙的想法
And each year new and
每年都有新的
transformative apps are
变革性的 App
introduced bases on those ideas.
在这些想法的基础上变为现实
And each time this happens you
你们每一个想法的实现
take creativity to new levels.
都把创造力提升一个高度
For example, take a look at the
我们来看一下
last three years of Apple Design
过去三年 Apple Design Award
Award winners.
设计大奖的得主
There are incredible games here.
其中有精彩的游戏
Powerful design tools.
强大的设计工具
New workflow solution, new video
全新的工作流解决方案
workflow solutions.
全新的视频工作流解决方案
Innovative photography tools.
极具创意的摄影工具
Apps that empower health and
能够帮助人们
fitness.
保持健康的 App
Music creation and DJing tools.
音乐制作和 DJ 工具
And apps to better understand
甚至还有能帮你了解
human anatomy.
人体结构的 App
As well as everyday tools that
此外 还有一些日常工具
help you to get things done and
能帮你完成计划
make a, truly make a difference
真正地在影响
in this world.
这个世界
The developers of these apps and
这些 App 的开发者
so many more over the years have
还有许多开发者 在过去的这些年里
amazed us with their excellent
用他们出色的作品惊艳了我们
Now, we all understand the
我们都知道
incredible hard work that goes
在这些出色的 App 的
into the design and development
设计和开发过程中
of great apps like these and
会经常遇到无数
others.
难以想象的困难
We're all too familiar with the
我们都经历过
long nights, long hours,
那些漫长的夜晚 长时间的工作
technical hurdles, design
技术上的难关和设计上的挑战
challenges, and honestly, often,
并且 说实话
a really hard to find bugs.
Bug 通常很难找到
But that's why we're here
但是这也是我们今晚
tonight.
在这里相聚的原因
To honor and celebrate that hard
为了感谢并嘉奖
work.
那些辛苦的付出
Today's winners set a new
今晚的获奖者
benchmark in creativity and they
为创造力树立了新的基准
demonstrate the mark of
他们用出色的作品
brilliance that makes something
证明了自己卓越的才能
Okay. We've got something to do
好 今晚我们
here, tonight, which is to give
将在这里
out a bunch of awards.
颁发许多奖项
And we're going to do that in a
而我们的颁奖厅
very large room.
非常的大
So, if you hear your name
因此 如果你们听见叫到自己的名字
called, if you hear your app's
或者听见叫到你们 App 的名字
name called, you need to make it
你们要快点上台
Because we want to move this
因为我们不想把时间拖得很久
along and it's a big room.
并且这个房间实在是太大了
There are two sets of stairs
这有两组台阶
here on either side of me.
在我两边各一组
So, just head towards me, you'll
所以 你往我这边走
find a set of stairs, you'll
就会看见台阶
make it onto the stage, and
走到舞台上来
we'll move on from there.
然后我们就能继续了
So, let's get started.
我们开始吧
Identifying the audience for
为你的 App 找到目标用户
your app and developing
并且为他们
something that's perfectly
和他们的需求
suited for them and their needs
量身打造一个 App
is really important.
非常重要
The developer of our first
今天第一个获奖者
winner today built an app that's
开发了一个 App
perfectly tuned for children and
它非常适合孩子
the way that they learn.
和孩子的学习方式
Join me in congratulating
让我们有请
Bandimal by Yatatoy.
《BANDIMAL》的开发者 Yatatoy
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
All right.
好的 《BANDIMAL》 是一个有趣且直观的
intuitive music composer app.
音乐创作 App
It lets kids explore music and
它能够使孩子探索音乐
be the maestro of their own
并指挥自己的
animal band.
动物乐队
And the key to this app is its
这个 App 的核心
focus on creativity.
是创造力
There are no rules, no notes, no
没有规则 没有音符
chords, no scores.
没有和弦 没有打分
Let's take a look.
我们来看一看 Andrea
Andrea.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 John
Let's dive right in.
我们来体验一下
I'll tap on the plus here to
我点击这个加号
start a new composition.
来创建一个新的编曲
And the music gets started right
音乐会立刻
away,
开始响起
which we should hear, soon.
我们马上就会听到 就像这样
But we're going to need to add
但是我们需要添加
some notes.
一些音符
The app has this adorable cast
这个 App 有这些可爱的动物角色
of animal characters.
可以选择
Each one makes a different
每个动物可以发出不同的声音
I'm going to swipe through them
我把每个角色都试一下
till I find one that I like,
直到找到自己喜欢的那个
which I guess, I'm going to go
我想我会选
with this buffalo, here.
这头水牛
I'll tap down here with my
我在这里
finger to add some notes.
用手指轻点添加音符
And you can see each note comes
你会发现不同的音符
with its own special dance move.
会有不同的舞蹈动作
Now, I'm going to speed up the
现在 我要通过转动这个按钮
tempo by turning this dial.
来加快节奏
And, maybe, after I do that I
然后我想让
decide I want to give my buffalo
我的水牛
a nice rest every other beat.
在隔一拍都休息一下
There we go.
就像这样
Now, I need a nice lead singer
现在 我需要一个好的领唱
to complement my buffalo bass,
来补充水牛的低音
so I'm going to tap here, swipe
轻点这里
through my options.
边滑动边挑选 像这样
This chicken looks like she'll
这只小鸡看起来能成为一个明星
Tap down here.
点这里 我们要加快它的节奏
tempo to match my buffalo bass.
使它和水牛的低音节奏同步
And, maybe, I'll do a call and
我想要那种一呼一应的效果
response type thing so they can
这样它们就能
interact with each other.
与彼此互动了
Now, I need one more animal to
现在我还需要一个动物
spice things up.
来让音乐更丰富一点
So, I'm going to tap here.
所以我轻点这里
I happen to know there's a
我刚好知道
particularly funky jellyfish
有一只很时髦的水母
here.
所以我们来试试这个
Now, let's listen.
现在我们听一下
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
Sounds good.
听起来不错 当孩子们作曲时
compositions they're building
在培养他们的节奏感
musicality, very playfully and
和乐感 这非常有趣
naturally, without need for any
也非常自然 不需要任何
prior musical knowledge.
音乐的背景知识
And the beauty of the app is any
这个 App 的亮点
combination of notes is going to
在于不论如何组合音符
sound good, because it's all
都很好听 因为所有音乐
playing in pentatonic scale.
都使用五声音阶
So, there's always a feeling of
所以它总能
success.
给你带来成就感
Let's check out this percussion
我们来看看上面这个
section, up here.
打击乐器部分
So, I'm going to add some high
我们添加一些踏跋
hat there.
在这添加小鼓和
some more percussion, here.
更多的打击乐器
And lastly, my bass drum.
最后加入低音鼓
All of these sounds, percussion
所有的声音 包括打击乐
and animals, were recorded in
和动物的声音都是
the studio using real
在录音棚里
instruments to get the music and
使用真实的乐器
natural sounds.
录制成的
I can even add a sound effect by
我还可以通过点击这些小山图标
tapping on these mountains.
添加一些声音效果
That's going to give my chicken
这样会使我的小鸡
an echo.
产生混响
So, let's check out this
我们来听一下
reverberating chicken.
这只加了混响的小鸡
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
So, you can see there's all
你可以看到
sorts of fun to be had with
这个 App 里的各种声音
sound in this app.
将会带来很多乐趣
And it's a great way for kids to
这对于孩子来说是一个很好的方式
get creative with music and feel
来培养音乐创造力
their ear and their intuition
锻炼他们的耳朵
for the rhythms and sounds that
让他们更直观地
they like to hear together.
感受到声音和节奏
The Yatatoy team of three spent
Yatatoy 的三人团队
two years developing this app
花了两年时间开发这个 App
using Swift, Sprite Kit, and
他们使用了 Swift SpriteKit
Core Audio.
和 Core Audio
They were working remotely
他们一直在远程协作
between Helsinki and Vienna.
有人在赫尔辛基 有人在维也纳
And they were doing this in the
并且他们是利用
afterhours from their day jobs.
下班时间进行
It's all culminated in an app
最终他们成功的开发出了
that's really magical.
这个神奇的 App
So, congratulations.
祝贺他们
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Andrea.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Andrea
That's Bandimal.
这就是《BANDIMAL》
All right.
好的
Next up in an app developed by a
下面这个 App 的开发团队
team of two biologists; a
是由两个生物学家
physicist, and a chemist.
一个物理学家和一个化学家组成的
Both are long time Indie Mac
他们一直是 Mac 的独立开发者
developers and one of them is,
其中还有一个人
actually, a four-time Apple
事实上是第四次
Design Award winner.
获得 Apple Design Award 设计大奖
These guys teamed up to develop
这些人组成一个团队
our next app, which is Agenda by
开发出了下面这个 App
Momenta B.V. out of the
《Agenda》
Netherlands.
由荷兰的 Momenta B.V. 开发
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
So, Agenda takes a clever new
《Agenda》在 Mac 上开创了一个
approach to note taking on the
做笔记的新方式
Mac and now, on iOS, as well.
现在也已登陆 iOS 平台
By combining notes, calendars,
它将笔记 日历
and tasks in unique ways and
和任务通过独特的方式
with really powerful
整合在一起
relationships.
彼此之间联系紧密
And as well, it's got a great
同时它拥有
clean design.
简洁的设计
And we'd like to show it to you,
我们现在展示给你们看
now.
下面交给 Chris
&gt;&gt; Agenda is a simple and fresh
&gt;&gt; 《Agenda》用简单清新的方式
way to keep yourself organized.
让你的一切井井有条
It combines a To-Do list and a
它将待办事项
note taking app with a
记事本 与日历功能
delightful calendar integration.
优雅地整合在了一起
Let me show you what I mean.
让我给大家展示一下
We start out with On the Agenda.
我们从 “On the Agenda（在议程上）”开始
This is a task manager like
这是一个像任务管理器
experience.
一样的东西
I can quickly see my highest
我能够快速找到
priority items and what I need
最优先的事项和其他我需要
to do with all my prior notes
优先处理的事项 还会展示
attached.
我做的笔记
I can mark things off as I
如果它们已经完成
complete them.
我就可以勾选以归档
So, now that we're done with
比如 我现在已经完成了 “Keynote”
Keynote, let's get that off.
所以我们将它取消标记
And State of the Union.
“SOTU” 也完成了
Actually, in the midst of a
我正在装修房子
house renovation, so I need to
所以我需要记得
remember to call the contractor.
给装修公司打电话
It's super convenient to see all
能在打电话之前看到
my prior notes attached before I
所有重要的笔记
make that phone call.
真的很方便
What makes this app really great
这个 App 的出彩之处
is its integration with
在于它对日历的整合
So, on the right-hand side here,
因此在右手边这里
you can see all my Calendar
你可以看到我所有的
events.
日程安排
There's a HealthKit lab tomorrow
明天有一个 HealthKit 实验研讨
and I need to remember to note
我需要记得参加
down a couple of questions.
并记录一些问题
So, we'll do that together.
我们一起来看一下
So, I bring in this note.
我将这个事项拖进来
You can see it brings in all the
你可以看到所有的细节都被拖进来了
details from Calendar.
从日历里
So, the event details, the
包括活动的细节
location, the attendees.
地点和参会人员
So, I can focus on creating the
这样我可以专心做记录
So, as I create this note, you
在我做记录的时候
can see the app supports
你们可以看到
markdown.
这个 App 支持 Markdown
It also supports tagging, which
还支持添加标签
is really nice.
这个功能很棒
So, I'm going to tag this as a
我在这添加一个
HealthKit related note.
与 HealthKit 有关的笔记
As I'm making this note, I
当我记录这件事的时候
realize a colleague and I had a
我想起来我和一个同事
meeting a couple weeks back,
在几周前开了一个会
where we brainstormed some
会上进行了头脑风暴
HealthKit related questions.
提出了一些与 HealthKit 有关的问题
So, I'm going to swing over to
所以我会查找日历
Calendar and find that meeting.
找到那次的会议
This meeting with John.
和 John 的会议
Agenda provides this link in the
《Agenda》 设置了这样的链接
Calendar in my, so as I click on
在我的日历 这样我可以通过点击链接
this it clicks me right back
立刻找到
into this meeting with John.
与 John 的那次会议
And here are the questions that
这就是我想找的
I wanted.
那些问题
So, you can imagine after using
你可以想象一下
this for a couple weeks, you end
在使用这个 App 几周后
up with this really great
你会发现是如此的方便
integration with Calendar and
将日历和日常事项整合以后
And it keeps you super
它可以让你的一切
organized.
都井井有条
Lastly, because I know I'm going
最后 因为我知道我将会
to be doing a lot of HealthKit
在这周参加多场 HealthKit 讨论
talking this week, I'm going to
所以我会搜索
search for all my HealthKit
所有与 HealthKit
related events.
相关的活动
And I can save this as an
我可以将它们储存在
overview.
“Overview（概览）”下
And what this does, it creates
这样可以使建立一个
this nice little pocket here,
小的文件夹
where everything HealthKit
将所有与 HealthKit 相关的事项
related is in one spot.
都放在一起
Super convenient.
非常方便
The entire app is created in
整个 App 的开发
Swift and it leverages iCloud,
使用 Swift 语言编写
so it syncs across all of my
并且可以借助 iCloud
devices.
在我的所有设备上同步
Agenda is not simply a place to
《Agenda》不仅仅可以
store text.
储存文本
Rather, a tool that gently
还可以潜移默化地
reinforces great note taking
培养良好的记录习惯
Agenda is, also, available on
《Agenda》也可以在 iOS 上使用
iOS and makes a great addition
它可以极大的
to your productivity arsenal.
提高你的工作效率
Thank you.
谢谢 祝贺
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Chris.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Chris
Great apps always leave a strong
好的 App 总是能让人
impression, and then reinforce
印象深刻 并且
it again and again, every time
在我们每一次使用它们的时候
that we use them.
我们对它们的喜爱都会加深一点
With amazing visuals, excellent
有着令人惊叹的画面
onboarding, a relaxing
极佳的上手体验
soundtrack, and great gameplay,
令人放松的音乐和精彩的游戏情节
join me in welcoming Alto's
下一个获奖作品是
Odyssey as your next winner.
《阿尔托的奥德赛》
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
This is an app that we fell in
这是一个我们
love with, just like we did with
非常喜爱的一款 App
its predecessor.
就像我们喜爱它的前作一样
Snowman and Team Alto have done
Snowman 和 Team Alto
an incredible job of taking what
付出了很多努力
people love from Alto's
保留了《Alto's Adventure》中
Adventure and improving on it in
人们喜爱的部分并在
every way for Odyssey.
《阿尔托的奥德赛》中全面提升
And I'd like to ask my
我现在想请
colleagues, Adrienne and Jordan,
我的同事 Adrienne 和 Jordan
to show it to us, now.
为大家展示
&gt;&gt; Thanks, John.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 John
Alto's Odyssey is an endless
《阿尔托的奥德赛》是一个无尽头的
sandboarding game, where you
滑沙游戏
ride through sunswept dunes,
你穿梭于洒满阳光的沙丘
perform midair stunts, all while
表演空中特技
completing fun challenges and
同时完成有趣的挑战
unlocking new characters.
并解锁新角色
So, my colleague Adrienne will
我的同事 Adrienne
be joining us for the demo,
今天将会
today.
给我们试玩
So, let's get started.
我们开始吧
The first thing that we loved
我们喜爱《阿尔托的奥德赛》的
about Alto's Odyssey was that it
第一点是
provides the user with
它会优雅地暂停游戏
contextual clues and elegantly
并且为玩家提供
pauses the game, so the player
背景提示 这样玩家
learns by playing.
就可以边学边玩
So, here she's getting taught
现在她正在学习
how to perform a wall ride,
如何在墙上滑行
which is a new feature in the
这是游戏中的一个新特性
There are no carousels that
游戏没有设置其他角色
she's swiping through.
在她的滑行的过程中
It's just her and the game.
整个游戏只有她一个人
We, also, love that it maintains
我们也很喜欢它保持了
that same simple control scheme
《Alto's Adventure》中简洁的操作模式
for Alto's Adventure but ramps
但是增加了
up the difficulty with new
新的挑战
challenges.
来提升游戏难度
Control-wise, all Adrienne is
操作方面 Adrienne 需要做的只有
doing is tapping to jump, and
轻点跳跃
then tapping and holding to
或用长按来表演
perform some epic flips.
优美的空中翻转
Now, Alto's Odyssey is a real
《阿尔托的奥德赛》是一场
feast for the senses.
名副其实的感官盛宴
Visually, there's so much to
视觉方面
look at in this game.
有许多值得称道的地方
There is elements in the
有许多元素
foreground, in the background
在前景和背景中
like hot air balloons, sand
比如热气球
coming off the back of the
滑板尾部
board.
扬起的沙子
But each level has such a
每个关卡
striking color palette to it
也都会有不同的配色
that we fell in love with.
这正是我们爱上它的原因
That same attention to detail,
对细节的关注
also, carries over into the
同样也体现在声音效果上
So, actually, let's take a
那么 我们现在就来听一下
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
Ah. Again, we love this.
我们真的很喜欢它
And you can, actually, listen to
你也可以随时听
it, too, because it's available
因为原声带已经可以
on iTunes and Apple Music.
iTunes 和 Apple Music 中上架了
We, also, fell in love with how
我们也喜欢
it uses the haptic engine on our
它对我们设备上的触感引擎的支持
So, Adrienne is getting a slight
当 Adrienne 在游戏中跳跃落地时
vibration on the iPhone when
在墙壁上滑动时
she's, when she's landing a
或是在热气球上弹跳时
even, bouncing off of hot air
她的 iPhone 都会
balloons in the game.
微微震动一下
It, also, maintains a super
同时 它还十分流畅
smooth 60 frames per second on
它在所有设备上
every device, including previous
都能达到 60 帧每秒的帧率
generation devices.
包括上一代设备
In large part, thanks to Metal 2
这很大程度上得益于
and Unity.
Metal 2 和 Unity
And it even maintains that same
它还在所有设备保留了
simple control scheme across
相同简洁的操作模式
iPhone, iPad, and Apple TV.
不论在 iPhone iPad 上还是 Apple TV 上
So, Alto's Odyssey is localized
所以《阿尔托的奥德赛》 已经
into an incredible 20 languages,
本地化为 20 种语言
has over 2,000 4.5-star ratings
在它发布的短短四个月以来
since launching just over four
已经获得了超过 2000 个
months, ago.
平均为 4.5 星的评分
And is available only on the
它只能在
iPhone, iPad, and Apple TV.
iPhone iPad 和 Apple TV 上使用
So, again, congratulations to
这是游戏中的这个团队
And back to you, John.
舞台交还给你 John
Great going, guys.
做得好 各位
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; So, great.
&gt;&gt; 太棒了
Now, talking about localization,
谈到本地化
localizing your app so that it's
本地化你的 App
available to people around the
让其他国家的人
world in their language of
能选择他们自己的语言
choice is really important.
来使用你的 App 是非常重要的
And it's something that we talk
这是我们
about a lot, here at Apple.
在 Apple 经常谈论的问题
And we encourage you to do.
我们鼓励你们去这样做
But making an app that helps
但是使一个 App 能够帮助人们
people converse with others
和其他使用不同语言的人交流
is a big deal.
是一件很了不起的事情
Our next winner is an app that's
我们下一个获奖的 App
been downloaded more than 80
被下载了超过
million times.
八千万次
Join me in congratulating
让我们祝贺
iTranslate Converse, by
《iTranslate Converse 语音翻译》
iTranslate.
开发者是 iTranslate
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
So, founded in 2009, iTranslate
iTranslate 成立于 2009 年
is an Austrian company based in
是一个奥地利公司
the city of Graz, famous for
总部在格拉茨
being the birthplace of Arnold
它因为是阿诺·施瓦辛格的故乡而被人熟知
But it's now, also, famous for
但现在 它还因为
being the birthplace of this
是这个 App 的故乡而被人熟知
What sets this app apart is its
这个 App 的出众之处在于
support for 38 languages and its
它支持 38 种语言
simple UI that enables everyday
并且它简洁的用户界面
conversations between people.
可以帮助人们进行日常交流
Let's take a look at how this
我们来看一看它是如何工作的
Paulo, Carol.
Paulo Carol
&gt;&gt; Thank you, John.
谢谢 John
iTranslate Converse is available
&gt;&gt; iTranslate Converse 只能在
only on iOS and was completely
iOS 上使用 并且它全部由
developed using Swift.
Swift 语言编写
Thanks to its straightforward
它直观的设计
design and intuitive user
和用户界面
interface the app is super easy
使它非常易于使用
All you need to do is swipe up
你需要做的就是向上滑动
and then, pick two out of the 38
然后在支持的 38 种语言中
languages available.
选择两种语言
Ah, German.
选择德语
What would Arnold say to you,
看看施瓦辛格
today?
想对你说什么
[German language] Ich komme
[ 德文 ]“Ich komme wieder”
&gt;&gt; I'll be back.
我会回来的
&gt;&gt; But for the purpose of this
为了更好地展示
demo, we're going to pick
我们接下来选择
Chinese Mandarin.
中文普通话
Now, as you can see, the whole
你可以看到
screen of the app turns into a
整个屏幕都是变成了
tappable area.
可点击区域
But the developer went one step
但是开发者进一步
further by implementing 3D touch
应用了三维触控
and haptic feedback.
和触感引擎功能
So, you can use the app without
所以 你可以使用这个 App
even looking at the screen.
即使在不看屏幕的情况下
Now, let's imaging I have just
假如我刚刚
landed in Beijing and I'm
飞到北京
meeting my colleague, Carol.
我见到了我的同事 Carol
And I'm super hungry but I don't
我非常饿 但是
speak a single word of Chinese.
我一点中文都不会
So, Carol, do you know where to
Carol “Do you know where to have
have spaghetti?
spaghetti?”
[ Chinese Language ]
[ 中文 ]
&gt;&gt; Why do you want to eat
&gt;&gt; “为什么你想
spaghetti in Beijing?
在北京吃意大利面”
[ Laughter ]
[ 笑声 ]
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Because, I'm, oops, sorry.
&gt;&gt; 因为我 哦 抱歉
Because, I am Italian.
“Because, I am Italian.”
[ Chinese Language ]
[ 中文 ]
&gt;&gt; Actually, the spaghetti was
&gt;&gt; “其实，意大利面
invented in China.
是在中国发明的”
[ Chinese Language ]
[ 中文 ]
&gt;&gt; Let's go and try the
“让我们去试一下
authentic Chinese food.
地道的中国菜吧
Want to eat roast duck?
想吃烤鸭吗？”
&gt;&gt; That sounds delicious.
&gt;&gt; “That sounds delicious.”
[ Chinese Language ]
[ 中文 ]
&gt;&gt; So, iTranslate Converse is,
《iTranslate Converse 语音翻译》
also, available on Apple Watch,
也可以在 Apple Watch 上使用
where users can access the app
用户可以通过复杂功能来
via complication.
使用这个 App
On Apple Watch Series 3 you can
在 Apple Watch Series 3 上 你可以
use the app even without your
在没有连接 iPhone 的情况下
iPhone.
使用这个 App
Now, let me finish by saying
最后 我用一个
something to you in a more
你们更加熟悉的语言来结束这个演示
familiar language.
[ 意大利文 ]“Ricordatevi di installare
[ Foreign Language ]
questa app prima di andare all'estero.”
&gt;&gt; Remember to install this app
&gt;&gt; 在你出国之前
before going abroad.
记得安装这个 App
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ][ 意大利文 ]&gt;&gt; “Grazie e buon
[ Foreign Language ]
divertimento alla conferenza sviluppatori.”
&gt;&gt; Thank you and have fun at the
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 祝你在开发者大会上
Developers Conference.
玩得开心
&gt;&gt; Back to you, John.
&gt;&gt; 舞台交还给你 John
&gt;&gt; Good night.
&gt;&gt; 晚安 做得好
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
That's awesome.
太棒了
That's an app that can break
这款 App
down barriers and help us build
能够消除障碍
meaningful relationships with
并且帮助我们
people we, with whom we don't
与那些语言不通的人
speak their language.
结为朋友
Now, when we judge apps for the
当我们为 Apple Design Award 设计大奖
Apple Design Awards we're
评判 App 的时候
looking for apps that are
我们想要的 App 应该有
incredibly well designed, that
完美的设计
are innovative, and they're
具有创新性
optimized for our devices.
并在我们的设备上有很好的优化
Next up is as wonderful
下一个获奖的是一个优秀的
puzzle-adventure platformer for
解谜冒险游戏
iPhone, iPad, and Apple TV
可以在 iPhone iPad 和 Apple TV 上使用
that's all of these things and
它具有我所说的一切优点
more.
却不仅限如此
Please, join me in
有请《Playdead's INSIDE》
Playdead.
的开发者 Playdead
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
Developed by Playdead in
这款游戏由 Playdead 在哥本哈根开发
Copenhagen, INSIDE is a
《Playdead's INSIDE》是一个
beautiful and frightening
唯美而有些恐怖的
adventure game with almost
冒险游戏 它在 App Store 中
10,000 4.5-star reviews on the
得到了近万个
App Store.
平均为 4.5 星的评价 难以置信
And to show it to you, now, I'd
现在来给你们展示一下
like to ask Mark and Adrienne.
有请 Mark 和 Adrienne
&gt;&gt; Thanks, John.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 John
INSIDE is an eerie adventure
《Playdead's INSIDE》是一个恐怖冒险游戏
filled with intrigue and danger.
充满阴谋与危险
You play as an unnamed boy as he
玩家作为一个没有姓名的男孩
struggled through a dystopian
要努力逃出一个
world.
反乌托邦的世界
By solving puzzles, you uncover
通过解开谜题 你会揭露
an alarming environment of
令人战栗的世界
lifeless bodies and their
那里充斥着行尸走肉和
violent controllers.
暴力的操纵者
But buried under this dark
但在这个黑暗的设定下
premise is a brilliantly
却有着一个
designed game.
设计如此出色的游戏
A worthy successor to Playdead's
《Playdead's INSIDE》继承了 Playdead 的
first game, Limbo, INSIDE also
第一个游戏《地狱边境（Limbo）》的特点
uses a monochromatic palette,
使用单一的色彩
which places your focus solely
让你们的注意力只集中在
on the details of the
环境和动画
environment and the animation.
这些细节上
Check it out as he actually
可以看到 当他
pulls and struggles to get these
费力拉下墙上的木板
boards off the wall.
呈现的效果太酷了
INSIDE's chilling soundtrack
《Playdead's INSIDE》
reinforces its sinister
中令人恐惧的配乐加强了
atmosphere.
其险象环生的氛围
Playdead's audio designers,
《Playdead's INSIDE》的音效设计师
actually, used a contact
将接触式麦克风
microphone on a human skull to
放在人的头骨上
create many of the sound effects
创造出了你在游戏中
that you hear in the game.
听到的音效
Let's listen in.
我们来听一下
[ Scraping Sound ]
[ 刮擦声 ]
[ Bang Sound ]
[ 碰撞声 ]
[ Running Footsteps ]
[ 奔跑脚步声 ]
With no onboarding at the
游戏没有设置新手教学
beginning and no loading screen
中间也没有加载界面
in the middle, INSIDE is both
《Playdead's INSIDE》的游戏体验是
intuitive and immersive.
直观且沉浸的
Using Unity, Metal, and a custom
使用 Unity Metal 和一个专门的
temporal reprojection filter,
时间重投影滤镜（temporal reprojection
Playdead's crafted this
filter） Playdead 创造出了
distinctly surreal environment
逼真的超现实主义环境
and console quality graphics.
和主机级的高品质画面
They actually fully support HDR
它在 iPhone X 和
on both the iPhone 10 and the
iPad Pro 上
iPad.
完全支持 HDR
So, that makes dark scenes like
所以 这使所有的黑暗场景
this seem really crisp and
看起来都十分锋利清晰
Now, light plays an important
光影在这个游戏中
role on INSIDE, and roving
是一个重要的元素
spotlights are, often, your
摆动的聚光灯通常
enemies.
是你的敌人
But, in this case, Adrienne has
但是 在这种情况下
to, actually, turn the lights on
Adrienne 必须要打开灯
in order to power that elevator
来使走廊尽头的电梯正常工作
The shadows cast by the
聚光灯照射产生的阴影
spotlights provide some respite,
可以使你稍作休息
but you're never safe for long.
但你不会一直都很安全
iCloud, actually, allows you to
iCloud 可以在设备间
save your progress across
保存你的游戏进度
devices, so you can pick back up
所以你可以随时接着玩
where you left off, whether
不论你是在 iPad 上
iPhone, or on Apple TV.
还是在 iPhone 或 Apple TV 上玩
Now, I don't want to spoil too
我并不想过多的剧透
much of the game for you, but
这个游戏
there's one more scene I want to
但是我还想展示一个画面
And fair warning; it's a little
友情提示
intense.
这个镜头比较刺激 我们看一下
[ Heavy Breathing And Running
[ 沉重的呼吸声和
Footsteps ]
奔跑脚步声 ]
[ Splashing Sounds ]
[ 水声 ]
[ Running Footsteps ]
[ 奔跑脚步声 ]
[ Eerie Sounds ]
[ 恐怖的声音 ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ 枪声 ]
[ Dogs Barking In Distance ]
[ 远处狗吠声 ]
[ Dogs Barking Closer ]
[ 狗吠声靠近 ]
[ Splash ]
[ 落水声 ]
INSIDE is a beautifully designed
《Playdead's INSIDE》是一个设计精良
and brilliant adventure game and
并且十分出色的冒险游戏
a worthy winner of an Apple
是 Apple Design Award 设计大奖
Design Award.
实至名归的获得者
Congratulations.
祝贺
Well done.
很棒
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Well done.
&gt;&gt; 很棒
Such a great game.
真是一个出色的游戏
Now, you know when you have a
你是否有
favorite movie or a favorite
非常喜欢的一部电影 或者一本书
book you just want to watch or
想要反复观看或阅读
Next up is an app that's like
下面这个 App 就会让你
that.
有类似的感觉
But you get to play the main
你要扮演
character and experience the
主人公并且通过
world through her eyes.
她的眼睛来体验这个世界
Our next winner is Florence by
下一个获奖的是《Florence》
Mountains.
开发者是 Mountains
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
So, Florence is a beautiful
《Florence》是一个浪漫的电影故事
cinematic story in which you get
游戏中你可以体验
to experience the impact of
主人公的生活和初恋
decisions and emotions of adult
感受她做出的决定 产生的情绪
life and first love.
以及它们所带来的影响
Let's take a look.
我们来看一下 Lauren
&gt;&gt; Thanks, John.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 John
I really enjoy playing Florence,
我非常喜欢玩《Florence》
because it is just so compelling
因为它很吸引人
and approachable.
玩起来又很容易
And it's really personal,
它是非常私人的
because you hold the story of
因为你手中可以掌握
Florence in your hand and use
《Florence》的整个故事
really familiar controls to
并使用熟悉的操作来玩
play.
通过浪漫的画面
soundtracks, and haptics, you
音乐和触觉
experience life as Florence.
你可以体验主人公的生活
In this scene it's all about
这个游戏全都是关于成年人的生活
And this game helps you realize
这个游戏帮助你意识到
that we're all just trying to
那些我们每天都在尝试
get through our day, to get back
去做的事情
to the things that we really
找到那些我们
care about.
真正在乎的事情
Another part of adult life, as
成年人生活的另一部分
well; getting calls from Mom.
接妈妈的电话
And this part of the game was
对我来说
just too real for me.
十分真实
It's like, ''Hi, Mom.
比如“喂 妈
No, I don't need any help
不 我不需要
finding a boyfriend.
你帮我找男朋友
And yes, work is going just
是的 工作一切顺利”
So, with the help of TC, who's
要感谢 TC 的帮助
doing a great job demoing today,
他在今天的展示中做得很棒
we're going to take a look at
现在我们来看一下
another scene.
另一个场景
Florence has a custom composed
《Florence》的音轨是原创的
soundtrack and it's incredible.
并且非常好听
Music plays a huge part
音乐在整个游戏体验中
experience.
占了很大一部分
And this is when you hear music
当你听到音乐
and you decide to tap the notes
轻点提示
to follow it.
并跟随它
And you know how music can make
你能感受到音乐
you feel, how it can just lift
它能够给你以力量
Well, it also can lead to a
它还可以带给你
really great story.
一个非常棒的故事
Through beautiful fades,
通过精美的淡入淡出
transitions, and soundtrack,
场景的变换和音乐的呈现
this plays just like a great
这款游戏就像是一部电影
And the camera holds on moments
镜头的短暂停顿
that mean just a little bit
让这些瞬间更有意义
more.
它精巧的设计
well, it makes you want to be
使你想要
more present in your own life
更多的感受自己的生活
and in your own relationships.
和自己的人际关系
So, how does it turn out with
那么 与另一个角色的关系
this other character?
会怎样发展呢
Well, you're just going to have
你去玩一下游戏
to play the game to find out.
就会知道了
There's a reason why people have
每个人都拥有初恋故事
a first love story.
是有原因的
Because, it's powerful,
因为初恋具有强大的力量
emotional, and it has an impact.
很情绪化 并且影响深远
And if you haven't experienced
如果你还没有经历过
it yet, well, this game is a
那么这个游戏是
wonderful preview to the real,
是一个很好的试验
honest, heart racing, and heart
体验那种真实 诚实 心跳加速
wrenching roller coaster that is
并伴随着心痛的过山车般的体验
first love.
这就是初恋
So, go for it.
所以试试吧
Play the game of first love.
尝试一下这个关于初恋的游戏
It's an incredible unforgettable
它将会是一个令人难忘的旅程
Congratulations, Florence.
祝贺《Florence》
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Lauren.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Lauren
State of the art apps support
最先进的 App 能够支持
the latest devices, the latest
最新的设备
OS's, an integrate with our
最新的操作系统
latest technologies.
整合我们最新的技术
Our next winner is a state of
下一个获奖的是一个最先进的
the art and beautifully crafted
设计精美的
smart calculator app called
小巧的计算器 App
Calzy from India.
叫做《Calzy 3》 来自印度
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
So, this is Raja.
这是 Raja
Calzy was created in an effort
《Calzy 3》的开发
to rethink the conventional
是对传统计算器的再思考
It's an incredibly customizable
它是一个可定制的
really well-designed app.
设计精良的 App
And it uses a ton of iOS
它将会是一个 iOS 技术
It's available for iPhone, iPad,
它可以在 iPhone iPad
Apple Watch, Messages, and even
Apple Watch “信息” App
as a Today widget.
甚至今天小组件中使用
I'd like to ask my colleague,
我想请我的同事
Tyler, to show it to you, now.
Tyler 展示给你们看
&gt;&gt; Thanks, John.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 John
Calzy has a fantastic formula
《Calzy 3》对创新
for innovation, combining great
有一种独到的见解
design with the clever use of
它将优秀的设计与
iOS technologies.
智能的 iOS 技术相结合
Let's have a look.
我们来看一看
There's Calzy, sweet as pi.
这就是《Calzy 3》 像派一样诱人
As you can see, right there,
就像你们能够看到的
it's got a simple yet elegant
它的设计简洁美观
And have a look at this, great
看一下这个
minds think alike.
英雄所见略同
So, Calzy does everything you'd
《Calzy 3》可以做所有
expect a calculator to do.
计算器能做的事情
This single screen app is packed
这个单屏 App 有很多特性
with features revealed by using
在这个滑动菜单里
3D Touch and haptic feedback for
它就用到了三维触控和
these sliding menus.
触感引擎
Perfect for singlehanded use.
完美适应单手操作
And if that single hand happens
如果你单手操作时
to be your left hand the
使用的是左手
keyboard is fully adjustable.
键盘还可以调节
You can have different keyboard
你可以自定不同的键盘布局
layouts for the main app, as
并在主 App 中的
well as the widget and the
小组件里
iMessage's app for maximal
或是在“信息” App 中使用
flexibility.
非常灵活
The standard layout, as you see
标准的布局是这样的
Calzy, also, of course, supports
但《Calzy 3》当然
the scientific layout, no
也支持科学计算器
rotation necessary.
无需旋转
Now, I'm not really a math
我数学不好
person, so these are all just
所以这对我来说
kind of Greek to me.
有点像天书
But speaking of science, I was
但是说到科学
recently reading an article.
我最近读了一篇文章
At least, John smiled at that.
至少 John 也这么认为
article about a very ambitious
关于一个非常有野心的想法
effort to quantify the weight of
要去计算世界上
all the biomass on earth.
所有生物量的质量
And so, I went to the study and
我看了这个研究
I grabbed some of the numbers
并且抓取了一些数字
and I put them here in Calzy's
我将它们输入到
Bookmarks function, which is a
《Calzy 3》的“书签”里
really handy way to store
这是一个储存信息
information.
非常方便的方法
Here, we can see this is the sum
这个是世界上
of the biomass of all the taxa
所有生物质量的总和
And it's rendered in gigatons of
当然 它们是以数十亿吨的碳
carbon, of course.
为单位的
Anyway, the Bookmark stores both
书签功能既可以储存
the expression and the value.
表达式也可以储存数值
So, if we find a new form of
因此 如果我们发现了一种新的生命
life I can always update the
我可以随时
expression.
更新这个表达式
And then, the values themselves
然后 数字就可以
can, actually, be stored up here
储存在这里
in the memory area at the top of
位于屏幕上方的记忆区域
the screen, waiting patiently
我们可以在
for me to drag them into another
下次计算时
calculation.
再调用它
So, you're probably wondering,
你可能想知道
or at least I know in am, what's
至少我想知道
the prevalence of bacteria
在地球上细菌对人类的
versus people on the earth.
比例为多少
So, we go back in here to the
我们回到
Bookmark.
书签功能
I know you were wondering it.
我知道你们也很想知道
And you take a look, here, the
看一下 这里
weight of all bacteria on earth
世界上所有细菌的质量
is 70 gigatons.
是 700 亿吨
I'm going to put that in there.
我把它拖到这里
And then, we're going to divide
然后我们除以
that by the weight of all the
世界上所有人的质量
paltry .06 gigatons.
6000 万吨
Now, if you notice that you've
如果你发现
made a mistake, all you have to
有一个错误 你需要做的是
do is go into the expression, 3D
找到表达式
Touch on the operator, put the
在运算符号上使用三维触控功能
correct one in.
将正确的输入进去
And this way, you can see that
这样你会发现
the weight of tall bacteria is
所有细菌的质量
about 1,200 times greater than
是所有人的质量的
the weight of all people.
大约 1200 倍
That's a lot of bacteria.
细菌非常的多
So, wash your hands before
所以 朋友们
dinner tonight, folks.
在晚饭前请洗手
There's a lot more great things
《Calzy 3》还有许多强大的功能
Calzy can do that we don't have
我们没有足够的时间
a whole lot of time for.
来展示它们
But it's got support for things
它支持“接力”和 iCloud 同步
even Face ID, Touch ID
可以使用面容 ID 触控 ID
protection for the bookmarks,
来加密书签功能
Drag and Drop.
还支持拖放操作
Whole bunch of great things.
功能十分强大
Go ahead and check it out in the
赶快去 App Store
App Store.
试试看吧
But before we go, a quick note
在这之前 我们来快速了解一下
about the inspirational story of
这位开发者的
the developer behind it.
励志故事
Gentleman from a small village
他来自印度的一个小村庄
in India working as a visual
是一名视觉特效师
effects artist who decided he
他想要用另一种方式
wanted to harness his creativity
来展现自己的创造力
So, he taught himself Swift, as
所以他自学 Swift
you do.
真是不容易
And within just a few months,
在短短几个月里
was creating great iPhone apps,
就开发出了许多优秀的 iPhone App
including Calzy.
包括《Calzy 3》
Congratulations, Raja.
祝贺你 Raja
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt; 好的
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Great games are memorable.
好的游戏让人难以忘记
They're unique.
它们与众不同
They're artistic.
它们充满艺术美感
They're filled with personality.
它们充满个性
And they have great performance.
它们表现也十分出色
Our next winner has all those
我们下一个获奖作品拥有
characteristics.
所有的这些特点
Join me in congratulating Frost
让我们有请《霜 - FROST》的开发者
by Kunabi Brothers.
kunabi brother
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
&gt;&gt; Let's go right here.
&gt;&gt; 请站到这里
&gt;&gt; This is, actually, Kunabi
&gt;&gt; 这其实是 kunabi brother
Brothers' second time on stage,
第二次登上这个舞台
because another game of theirs,
他们的另一款游戏
called Blek, won an Apple Design
《手指画线 - Blek》 也在 2014 年获得了
Award in 2014.
Apple Design Award 设计大奖
They've now returned with a
他们再次回归带来了一个
beautiful and calming freeform
精美而令人放松的
puzzle game that offers a deeply
开放式解谜游戏 它打造了一个
immersive space where players
深度沉浸式的空间 可以使玩家
can interact with and experience
互动和体验
the natural phenomenon of
群体的自然现象
You've got to see this.
你一定要看一看这个
Mike Stern.
Mike Stern
&gt;&gt; Thanks, John.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 John
So, swarming behavior has
集群行为一直以来
inspired scientists and artists
赋予了科学家和艺术家
through the ages.
很多灵感
And now, it's inspired a really
而现在它启发了
gorgeous and inventive game.
一个开创性的出色游戏的诞生
Right from the level selection
在难度选择的
screen we can see this number
界面上我们可以看到数字 “1”
one is comprised of tiny little
是由许多微小的
light creatures swarming about.
发光生物群落组成
And as we switch between levels
当我们改变难易程度时
we can see them scatter and
我们可以看到它们分散开
reform giving us a preview of
又聚集起来的组成
what's to come.
新的数字
Now, when we get into the game
当我们进入到这个游戏
we see this stream of blue
我们会看到一簇
creatures enter the gameboard.
蓝色生物进入到游戏界面
And our objective, here, is to
我们在游戏中的目标是
help these little guys find
帮助这些小生物
their way back to their home
回到它们自己的母星
Now, Frost was designed for
《霜 - Frost》可以说是为触控而生
Touch and it really shows.
并且它的确展现了
Interactions are so simple and
互动可以如此的简单
intuitive and natural.
直观和自然
And just behold how graceful and
只需要一点点互动
beautiful the swarm is, just
你就能感受到
with a little bit of
集群运动是多么
interaction.
美丽优雅
It's really pretty.
真的很美
Now, it seems here that the
现在我们的目的
objective it to try to take some
是试着将这些蓝色生物中的
of the blue creatures to one
一部分带回到一个星球
planet and some to the other.
另一部分带回到另一个星球
So, to start over I simply tap
我们先随意
anywhere on the screen.
点击屏幕上的任意一处
And using multitouch I can draw
使用多点触控技术我可以
two paths to each planet.
建立两条通路分别到达两个星球
Now, when those yellow rings
黄色的圆圈像进度条一样
fill, that's when I know how
告诉我每个星球
many creatures each planet has
需要承载多少生物
Little bit more.
再多一点
And once it fills all the way,
当它完全被填满的时候
this really beautiful animation
会产生漂亮的动画效果
plays to let me know that the
让我知道
level is complete.
我已经完成这一关
And on iPhone, they use haptics
在 iPhone 上 他们使用触感引擎
to punctuate that animation and
来加强这个动画效果
other special moments.
和其他重要时刻
Now, every level in Frost is a
《霜 - Frost》中的每一关
work of art.
都堪比一件艺术品
But I want to skip ahead here to
但是我想跳过
a more advanced level and go
直接到达较高的难度
from number 4 to number 24.
从 4 级到 24 级
Now, as we progress through the
当我们不断增加游戏难度的时候
game we're introduced to new
不仅会有新的
creative challenges along the
很有创意的挑战等待着我们
But also, new species with
还也有新的物种
different types of swarming
产生的不同类型的
behaviors.
集群行为
So, on this level we have yellow
所以 在这个难度上我们有黄色
creatures and blue and red.
蓝色和红色的生物
And it seems, here, that my
在这里 我的目标是
creatures get to the yellow
让黄色的生物去黄色的星球
So, I just make a beeline from
因此我画一条直线
one place to another, but
连接两个星球
they're not responding.
但是它们没有任何反应
Blue ones don't really do
蓝色的生物
anything, either.
也没有反应
Maybe, if I bring the red ones
也许我将红色的生物带到这里
over here it'll do something.
会产生一些反应
Oh, we can see those blue
哦 我们可以看到那些蓝色的
creatures really scattered.
生物分散开了
Now, what I want to do is just
我想做的是在这
pause here, for a second, and
先暂停一下
just kind of enjoy this moment
欣赏一下这个《霜 - Frost》
that Frost creates for us.
为我们创造的美妙瞬间
The mood that it sets is so
游戏的氛围
ethereal, it's so soothing and
是非常空灵的
so tranquil.
十分舒缓与宁静
Watching these creatures move
这些生物的不断运动
around is really mesmerizing and
非常的迷人
kind of hypnotic.
好像一种催眠术
A lot of players will, actually,
很多玩家会
just kind of stop and enjoy this
暂停游戏来享受
experience and experiment and
这种体验和感觉
observe how the creatures
观察生物是如何对
respond to touch, and really
触控作出反应的
soak it in.
他们会沉浸其中
But, not me.
但是 我不是这样
I like winning.
我想要通关
So, I'm going to try to get the
所以我试着让
red creatures to move around,
红色的生物不断移动
pick up the blue creatures who
这会带着蓝色的生物移动
might give a lift to the yellow
进一步带着黄色的生物一起移动
And help them find their way
帮助黄色的生物找到自己的家
It's a crazy enough plan that I
这是一个疯狂的方案
think it just might work.
但是我认为它可行
Now, Frost offers hours and
《霜 - Frost》给你提供了
hours of gameplay.
无数小时的游戏时间
And the sheer beauty of watching
成千上万的独立的
thousands of individually
富有活力的生物
animating creatures move around
在你的 iPhone 或者 iPad 上移动
your iPhone or iPad is really
这样的美景真的令人心旷神怡
Now, in order to power this real
为了实现
time simulation, they needed
实时仿真 他们需要
Metal on iOS.
在 iOS 上应用 Metal
It's the only consumer mobile
这是市面上唯一的
device which has the
拥有足够的计算能力
computational power needed to
来运行这个复杂的
render these complex
程序动画
programmatic animations.
的移动设备
But the thing that I love most
但是我最喜欢的是
about Frost is how anyone can
任何人都可以
play this game, regardless of
玩这款游戏
their age or where they live or
无论他们的年纪多大 居住在哪里
what language they speak.
或者使用什么语言
It can be a delightful, calming,
这都是一种愉快 沉静
and engaging experience.
吸引人的体验
This is a really beautiful game.
这是一款非常精美的游戏
Congratulations.
祝贺
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Mike.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Mike
You had most of us mesmerized,
你让我们都看入迷了
All right.
好的
Earlier, I spoke of code and
之前 我谈到过代码和创意
creativity, which when combined
当它们和技术结合起来
with technology can produce
就可以创造出
these transformative results.
这些变革性的成果
Our next winner is an app that
下一个获奖者是一个 App
is disrupting and uniquely
它影响着 改变着
changing things, how things are
人们完成任务的方式
Congratulations to Triton
祝贺 Triton Sponge
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
So, the developer here, Gauss,
它的开发者是 Gauss
is reinventing surgical care
致力于改造外科护理
using machine learning and
借助 iOS 上的机器学习
computer vision on iOS.
和计算机视觉来完成
And you've got to see this to
耳听为虚 眼见为实
So, let's take a look.
所以 让我们来看看吧
Here's Chris and Divia from our
这是我们健康团队的
Health Team to show you how it
Chris 和 Divia
works.
他们将展示如何使用这款 App
&gt;&gt; We love when teams tackle
&gt;&gt; 我们喜欢看团队
huge problems in unique ways.
以独特的方式解决大问题
Especially, in healthcare.
尤其是医疗问题
Today, many clinicians have no
今天 很多临床医生都很苦恼
idea how to estimate how much
没有办法测量
blood patients are losing in
救治过程中病人的失血量
As a result, a lot of clinical
所以 他们只能根据估测的结果
decisions are made based on
做出临床决策
guesstimation, which can lead to
这就会引发
all sorts of complications.
各种问题
Gauss Surgical is solving this
Gauss Surgical 用 iPad
problem using an iPad, machine
机器学习和计算机视觉
learning, and computer vision.
解决了这一问题
Before we show you a demo, I'd
在演示之前
like to introduce you to Chris
我想先做个介绍
and the tools we'll be using.
介绍一下今天使用的工具
We have an iPad Pro with an IR
我们有一个配备了
sensor, and some surgical
红外传感器的 iPad Pro
sponges that are used in
一些外科用纱布
operating rooms to soak up
用来在手术室里止血
Now, for the purposes of this
现在 为了演示
demo, we're going to mimic some
我们将用
fake blood by using some red
红色的食用色素仿造真正的血液
But if you start to feel queasy,
但是如果你感到难受
at all, please avert your eyes
可以转移一下视线
for just a moment.
只需一小会儿
Gauss' app is super simple to
Gauss 的 App 使用起来非常简单
All you have to do is hold up a
你只需要在镜头前
sponge in front of the camera.
将纱布展开
From there, Gauss uses Core ML
然后 Gauss 使用 Core ML
to detect the sponge using the
通过摄像机和红外传感器
camera and IR sensor.
来检测纱布
They've then developed some
他们还研发了
custom machine learning
自定义机器学习算法
algorithms to analyze the red
来分析纱布上
spots of blood and, actually,
一块一块的血迹
calculate blood loss.
最终计算失血量
It's amazing.
太神奇了
Gauss' app is FDA approved and
Gauss 的 App 是获得 FDA 批准的
HIPAA compliant.
符合 HIPAA 规范
But now, let's see if it's hippo
现在 我们就来看一下它
compliant.
是否符合两者的要求
As you can imagine.
你可以想象
As you can imagine, it's
想象一下
incredibly important in an
这是多么重要的
operating room to make sure you
能确保你在手术室里
don't accidentally double count
不会多数了一块纱布
So, if Chris hold up the hippo
所以 如果 Chris 在摄像机前
sponge one more time, even if in
将纱布多举了一次
a different orientation, Gauss'
即使是站在不同方位
app is able to detect that it's
Gauss 的 App 也能识别出
a duplicate and, actually, alert
这还是同一块纱布
Chris
提醒 Chris
to the duplication.
纱布拿重复了
That is amazing.
非常神奇
Gauss' app is being used in
Gauss 的 App 已经开始应用于
hospitals all across the country
全美国的医院
in labor and delivery use cases.
在孕妇生产中使用
And we couldn't be more excited
这个作品让我们
about their work.
无比兴奋
Congrats to the entire Gauss
祝贺 Gauss 的团队
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Awesome.
&gt;&gt; 太棒了 做的真好
That's pretty cool.
非常精彩
And our final award for this
今晚最后一个获奖的
evening goes to a brilliantly
是一个非常精彩的
executed platformer.
平台游戏
It's got a ton of personality,
有很多独特的个性
has great performance, a fun
操作流畅
soundtrack, and it's super
音乐有趣 很容易上瘾
addictive.
历时四年制作完成
Join me in celebrating our final
让我们欢迎最后一个获奖作品
winner, Oddmar by Mobge.
Mobge 游戏工作室制作的《奥德玛》
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
Oddmar was developed by a team,
《奥德玛》由一个团队共同开发
a small team of four, two of
团队共 4 个人 今天只有 2 个人
whom are here, at a university
来到了这里 他们都是
in Turkey, which goes to show
土耳其的大学生
that great games don't always
这说明 精彩的游戏
come from the places that you
并不是某个地区的专利
We've had a blast with this game
这款游戏让我们感到惊艳
and we think you will, too.
相信你们也会如此
We'd like to show it to you,
下面为大家展示这款游戏
Begum.
Begum
&gt;&gt; Thank you, John.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢你 John
Oddmar is a gorgeous
《奥德玛》是一个精彩绝伦的
action-adventure platformer that
动作冒险平台游戏
is beautiful, charming, and
它精美 迷人且幽默
Let us introduce you to Oddmar
我们将为大家介绍奥德玛
and our not so successful Viking
一个并不是很成功的维京人英雄
hero on the journey to prove
他将在旅途中证明
himself worthy of Valhalla.
他配得上英雄专属的瓦尔哈拉神殿 Adrienne
&gt;&gt; The onboarding is smooth and
&gt;&gt; 游戏的上手很流畅
the controls are easy to use
基于手势的操作
gesture controls.
十分简单
Simply, swipe left and right
简单说 用左手拇指左右滑动
with your left hand to move, and
来控制移动
up and down with your right hand
右手上下滑动
to jump.
来控制跳跃
Oddmar with its 24 handcrafted
《奥德玛》有 24 个手绘关卡
artistic levels in a Norse
它们来源于北欧神话故事
mythology storyline is full of
使整个游戏充满了
secrets and challenges.
神秘和挑战
As you travel through the
当你开始
adventures of Oddmar, from
奥德玛的探险之旅
magical forests to treacherous
从魔幻森林到诡异矿井
mines, beautifully animated
美丽的手绘动画场景
comic style cuts scenes between
在不同的关卡
the levels will help you find
都会帮助你找到通往
your way to Valhalla.
瓦尔哈拉神殿的路
The game really shines with its
游戏的视觉元素
visual elements, with beautiful
非常亮眼
scenic multiplane landscapes,
美丽如画的多重场景
lighting, and animation that
灯光和动画
almost brings it to life.
都使游戏栩栩如生
Oddmar, our Viking hero, is so
我们的维京人英雄奥德玛
brilliantly animated that it
有许多活灵活现小动画
puts a smile on your face,
一定能让你面带微笑
whether he's jumping on
不管是跳到蘑菇上
mushrooms, running through the
是穿过小河
rivers, or as he's simply
还是简单的
waiting for you to play.
等待你的指令 他都不会闲着
New game mechanics and controls
新的游戏机制和控制系统
are introduced for the player at
适合各种水平的玩家
And as the players progress
当玩家通过
through the levels, unique
不同关卡时
dangers and boss fights
有不同的危险和 Boss 战
challenges the players in new
以全新有趣的方式
and fun ways.
挑战玩家的胆量和技术
The game really does a fantastic
这个游戏真的非常棒
job of bringing excitement with
让人感到激动兴奋
every new character, control,
每一个新的角色 新的能力和关卡
and level, while introducing
都让人兴奋
these at a pace that allows the
新内容会徐徐引入
players to master it.
让玩家有足够的时间掌握
The soundtrack influenced by the
它的音乐受瑞典的
traditional Swedish folk music
传统民乐影响
really gives the game its Nordic
使北欧维京人风情
Viking setting at every level.
体现在游戏的每一个关卡
It was recorded at a studio in a
音乐是在瑞典南部
small village deep in the
森林深处的
forests of southern Sweden.
一个小村庄里录制的
So, every aspect of the game,
游戏的每一个方面
from level design to story to
从关卡设计到故事情节
music was made with great
再到音乐 都倾注了极大的心血
effort, dedication to detail,
非常注重细节
and craft.
精雕细琢
As visually stunning as it is
由于画面的细节
with the level of detail and
令人感到十分惊艳
artwork, Oddmar calls for a
《奥德玛》更适合在
larger screenplay and we think
大屏幕设备上游玩 我们认为
you will love it on iPad Pro.
你会喜欢在 iPad Pro 上玩这个游戏
It supports the use of game
它支持使用游戏手柄
controllers, allows you to play
也可以通过 iCloud 同步游戏进程
and sync on multiple devices by
让你能够在
saving on iCloud.
多台设备上游玩
Oddmar benefits from using Metal
《奥德玛》使用 Metal
to create this visually stunning
创造出了这种看起来震撼
and fluid gameplay experience.
玩起来爽快的游戏体验 它使用了
It uses only [inaudible]
按需加载资源（On-demand Resource）的模式
resources to reduce the initial
来减少游戏首次加载的时间
time to load by letting players
并且允许玩家
download the levels in the
在后台继续进行下载
background and has fun, colorful
玩家还可以和好友分享
image stickers to share with
《奥德玛》主题的
your friends.
好玩的彩色表情贴纸
Oddmar is localized into 12
《奥德玛》已经本地化至
languages and is only available
12 种语言
on iPhone and iPad.
仅在 iPhone 和 iPad 上可用
Well done to the Oddmar Team.
《奥德玛》团队真的做得很棒
Forward, Valhalla!
冲吧 向着瓦尔哈拉神殿
Back to you, John.
交给你了 John
&gt;&gt; Well done.
&gt;&gt; 非常棒
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So, that's Oddmar.
这就是《奥德玛》
So, these are our ten winners.
以上就是我们的 10 个获奖作品
Five incredible apps, five
5 个出色的 App
incredible games.
5 个精彩的游戏
Now, each winner receives the
现在 每个获奖者都拿到了
coveted Apple Design Award
梦寐以求的 Apple Design Award 设计大奖奖杯
trophy, which they've all been
他们把奖杯拿在手上
handed and are walking away
将带着奖杯骄傲地离开这里
This trophy is a solid piece of
奖杯由坚硬的铝片制成
aluminum that lights up when
触碰的时候就会发光
So, the Apple logo on top lights
顶部的 Apple Logo
up just like the top of your
就会像你们的 MacBook 一样亮起来
It's very cool and it's a
这非常酷
must-have.
也理所应当
It's definitely something to
这是一件值得珍藏的物品
collect and something to be
也是一个
super proud of.
值得骄傲的荣誉
Winners today, also, receive a
此外 今天的获奖者
prize package that includes
还会收到一份大礼包
almost one of everything that we
里面有几乎我们所有产品的
make in its best configuration.
顶级配置版
So, a 5K iMac Pro, a 15-inch
一台 5K iMac Pro 一台 15 英寸 MacBook Pro
MacBook Pro, a 256 GB iPhone 10,
一部 256 GB 的 iPhone X
a 512 GB iPad Pro with Apple
一部配备 Apple Pencil 的 512 GB iPad Pro
Pencil, a 4K Apple TV, an Apple
一台 4K Apple TV
Watch Series 3, and a set of
一块 Apple Watch Series 3
AirPods.
还有一套 AirPods
Not a bad haul.
还可以吧
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So, congratulations to all of
所以 衷心祝贺今晚所有的获奖者
And for the great work that
感谢他们为我们带来的优秀作品
they've done in the past year or
他们为此付出了过去一年甚至是
years, in some cases.
几年的心血
These ten apps set new standards
这 10 个 App 为 App 开发开创了新的标准
for innovation, design,
无论是在创新 设计
brilliance, execution,
精彩程度 制作
performance, creativity,
表现 创造力
craftsmanship, optimization,
技艺 优化
technology integration, and so
技术整合
much more.
还是其他方面
I want to thank you for joining
由衷的感谢
us, today.
你们今天的到来
It's been a long day, but we
这真是漫长的一天
appreciate your attendance.
谢谢你们来参加典礼
This is a special moment for all
这是一个对所有获奖者来说
of our winners.
非常重要的一刻
But it's, also, a special moment
但这个特殊的时刻
for you, their peers, and for
也属于你们 他们的行业同仁
our entire development
也属于我们整个开发社区
community, many of whom are
其中很多人
watching right now on the live
正在看我们的现场直播
So, thanks for joining us,
谢谢你们 与我们共渡
tonight.
这个美妙的夜晚
We're excited to see what you'll
我们也期待看到你们未来的作品
create, what you will create
看看经过这些获奖者的启发
next year inspired by these
你们明年会创造出什么
Check out their apps.
看看他们的 App
See what they've done.
看他们做了些什么
Learn from them.
向他们学习
They've done an incredible job.
他们做的非常棒
As well as being inspired by all
回想一下
of the new things that we
我们今天讲到的
announced, today.
新事物对你们的启发
Thanks for coming.
谢谢你们的到来
Good night.
晚安
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]